Hello Everyone This year we are celebrating
25 years of ICICI a journey built on hard
work, resilience and innovation.  ICICI
Lamb is a great team whose work culture and
team spirit is admired by all.  On this
outstanding achievement I Raghu Gulati would like
to dedicate a [music] song.
[Song voice] He fulfills every
[Music] promise He does every task with determination
[Music] May the name of ICI CI Lomba shine in the sky of Bhima
[Music] [Song voice] He fulfills every
promise
[Music] He gives [Song voice] He provides
excellent services He
never rests for a moment
[Music] He never leaves the hand of the one
whose [Music]
[Song voice] He
takes the
customer's
[Song voice] with complete devotion He makes every difficulty
easy [Music] May the
name of ICI CI Lomba shine in the sky of Seema [Song voice] He
fulfills every promise [Music]
[Music] There is no
one like him in claims [Music]
His identity is amazing [Song voice]
When it comes to security [Music] It comes on the lips,
such [Music] [Song voice] facilities are
provided even by the opponents [Music] He respects
Bhima [Song voice] He
shines in the sky [Music] The name of ICI CI Lomba
[Song voice]  [Voice] We
fulfill [Music] every promise The
leadership is new The team
[Song singing voice] [Music] The
old ones will write a new story together [Music]
P [Song singing voice] The goal of a thousand crores
[Music] is possible One
[Song singing voice] If one wants to
achieve this once, every heart will get this wish
[Music] [Song singing voice] The name
of ICICI Lom shines in the sky of Bhima [Music] The name of ICICI Lomba shines in the sky of Bhima [Song singing voice] We fulfill every
[Song singing voice] promise We do every work with determination [Music] We
fulfill [Music] [Song singing voice] every promise